{
    "words": {
        "kid": [
								{"question":"apple", "ans":"red fruit that starts with a A"},
								{"question":"ball", "ans":"used to play with a bat"},
								{"question":"bat", "ans":"used to hit a ball"},
								{"question":"bee", "ans":"its a insect that flies"},
								{"question":"bird", "ans":"they have wings"},
								{"question":"boy ", "ans":"a  young male"},
								{"question":"cat", "ans":"its a pet that meows"},
								{"question":"chair", "ans":"people sit on it"},
								{"question":"cold", "ans":"very low temperature"},
								{"question":"cow", "ans":"its meat is called beef"},
								{"question":"dad", "ans":"male parent; father"},
								{"question":"day", "ans":"time for Earth to make a complete rotation on its axis"},
								{"question":"dog", "ans":"its a pet that barks"},
								{"question":"egg", "ans":"we have it for breakfast"},
								{"question":"fan", "ans":"induces airflow for the purpose of cooling"},
								{"question":"fire", "ans":"it burns and produces flames"},
								{"question":"girl", "ans":"a young female"},
								{"question":"gold", "ans":"jewels  are made with it"},
								{"question":"horn", "ans":"it makes loud noise when you blow through it"},
								{"question":"horse", "ans":"its child is called a pony"},
								{"question":"hot", "ans":"high temperature"},
								{"question":"ice", "ans":"low temperature"},
								{"question":"jam", "ans":"sweet spread on breads"},
								{"question":"jet", "ans":"it flies very fast"},
								{"question":"jump", "ans":"to move upwards"},
								{"question":"king", "ans":"male ruler of a kingdom"},
								{"question":"light", "ans":"its not very heavy"},
								{"question":"lion", "ans":"its called the king of the jungle"},
								{"question":"man", "ans":"an adult male"},
								{"question":"mom", "ans":"female parent"},
								{"question":"monkey", "ans":"animal with tails that climbs trees"},
								{"question":"moon", "ans":"it comes up when the sun goes down"},
								{"question":"night", "ans":"its  dark with starts in the sky during this time"},
								{"question":"orange", "ans":"its a citrus fruit; also a color"},
								{"question":"pen", "ans":"uses ink to write"},
								{"question":"pencil", "ans":"used to write and it uses lead"},
								{"question":"phone", "ans":"you can call people using this and it rings when people call you"},
								{"question":"pig", "ans":"its meat is called pork"},
								{"question":"pretty", "ans":"beautiful"},
								{"question":"queen", "ans":"female ruler of a kingdom"},
								{"question":"sofa", "ans":"a chair that can seat more than one person"},
								{"question":"sun", "ans":"it produces light and hear; earth revloves around it"},
								{"question":"taxi", "ans":"a rental car"},
								{"question":"tiger", "ans":"its a big cat with yellow and black stripes"},
								{"question":"train", "ans":"it runs on rails and used to transport people"},
								{"question":"tub", "ans":"you fill it with water and use to wash the body"},
								{"question":"ugly", "ans":"not very pretty"},
								{"question":"vacuum", "ans":"used clean carpets"},
								{"question":"van", "ans":"a vehicle larger than a car"},
								{"question":"water", "ans":"its clear liquid and we drink it when we are thirsty"},
								{"question":"web", "ans":"its a trap created by a spider"},
								{"question":"whale", "ans":"its a large  mammal in the sea"},
								{"question":"women", "ans":"an female"},
								{"question":"zebra", "ans":"a animal like a horse with white and black stripes"},
								{"question":"zoo", "ans":"its a place where animals are kept"}

        ],
        "easy": [
								{"question":"abuse","ans":"to attack in words:REVILE"},
								{"question":"acme","ans":"the highest point or stage"},
								{"question":"acre","ans":"A unit of area in the U.S. Customary System, used in land and sea floor measurement"},
								{"question":"act","ans":"the process of doing: caught in the act."},
								{"question":"adore","ans":"to regard with loving admiration and devotion"},
								{"question":"aerate","ans":"to supply (the blood) with oxygen by respiration"},
								{"question":"aerial","ans":"of, relating to, or occurring in the air or atmosphere"},
								{"question":"align","ans":"to bring into line or alignment"},
								{"question":"amplify","ans":"to make larger or greater (as in amount, importance, or intensity):INCREASE"},
								{"question":"animal","ans":"any such living thing other than a human being"},
								{"question":"annoy","ans":"to disturb or irritate especially by repeated acts"},
								{"question":"answer","ans":"a spoken or written reply or response to a question,"},
								{"question":"antic","ans":"characterized by clownish extravagance or absurdity"},
								{"question":"appeal","ans":"to make an earnest request"},
								{"question":"apple","ans":"the usually round, red or yellow, edible fruit of a small tree"},
								{"question":"apt","ans":"unusually fitted or qualified:READY"},
								{"question":"archive","ans":"a place in which public records or historical documents are preserved"},
								{"question":"arm","ans":"the upper limb from the shoulder to the elbow"},
								{"question":"army","ans":"the military forces of a nation"},
								{"question":"arrest","ans":"to make inactive"},
								{"question":"art","ans":"the class of objects subject to aesthetic criteria; works of art collectively, as paintings, sculptures, or drawings"},
								{"question":"assert","ans":"to state or declare positively and often forcefully or aggressively"},
								{"question":"assess","ans":"to determine the importance, size, or value of"},
								{"question":"asset","ans":"the entire property of a person, association, corporation, or estate applicable or subject to the payment of debts"},
								{"question":"assume","ans":"to take to or upon oneself:UNDERTAKE"},
								{"question":"awe","ans":"an emotion variously combining dread, veneration, and wonder that is inspired by authority or by the sacred or sublime"},
								{"question":"baby","ans":"an infant or very young child"},
								{"question":"back","ans":"the rear part of the body"},
								{"question":"base","ans":"being of comparatively low value and having relatively inferior properties"},
								{"question":"bath","ans":"a washing or immersion of something, esp. the body"},
								{"question":"bed","ans":"a piece of furniture upon which or within which a personsleeps"},
								{"question":"bent","ans":"a strong inclination or interest:BIAS"},
								{"question":"bird","ans":"having a body covered with feathers and wings"},
								{"question":"bite","ans":"to cut, wound, or tear with the teeth"},
								{"question":"bitter","ans":"having a harsh, disagreeably acrid taste"},
								{"question":"blade","ans":"the flat cutting part of a sword, knife, etc."},
								{"question":"blow","ans":"(of the wind or air) to be in motion"},
								{"question":"boat","ans":"a vessel for transport by water"},
								{"question":"bread","ans":"a kind of food made of flour"},
								{"question":"canvas","ans":"a piece of cloth backed or framed as a surface for a painting"},
								{"question":"canyon","ans":"a deep narrow valley with steep sides and often with a stream flowing through it"},
								{"question":"cast","ans":"the set of actors in a dramatic production; to assign a certain role to (an actor)"},
								{"question":"census","ans":"a count of the population"},
								{"question":"chef","ans":"a skilled cook who manages the kitchen (as of a restaurant)"},
								{"question":"chorus","ans":"a body of singers who perform choral compositions"},
								{"question":"clog","ans":"something that shackles or impedes:ENCUMBRANCE"},
								{"question":"clot","ans":"a coagulated mass produced by clotting of blood"},
								{"question":"collapse","ans":"to fall or shrink together abruptly and completely"},
								{"question":"coma","ans":"a state of profound unconsciousness caused by disease, injury, or poison"},
								{"question":"comply","ans":"to conform or adapt one's actions to another's wishes, to a rule, or to necessity"},
								{"question":"concede","ans":"to grant as a right or privilege"},
								{"question":"concur","ans":"to act together to a common end or single effect"},
								{"question":"condemn","ans":"to declare to be reprehensible, wrong, or evil usually after weighing evidence and without reservation"},
								{"question":"condole","ans":"to express sympathetic sorrow"},
								{"question":"confess","ans":"to disclose one's faults; specifically :to unburden one's sins or the state of one's conscience to God or to a priest"},
								{"question":"confine","ans":"something that restrains"},
								{"question":"conform","ans":"to be similar or identical; also :to be in agreement or harmony"},
								{"question":"conquest","ans":"the act or process of conquering"},
								{"question":"conserve","ans":"to keep in a safe or sound state"},
								{"question":"console","ans":"to alleviate the grief, sense of loss, or trouble of:COMFORT"},
								{"question":"consult","ans":"COUNCIL, CONFERENCE; specifically :a deliberation between physicians on a case or its treatment"},
								{"question":"contempt","ans":"the act of despising:the state of mind of one who despises:DISDAIN"},
								{"question":"control","ans":"an individual or group used as a standard of comparison in a control experiment"},
								{"question":"convert","ans":"to bring over from one belief, view, or party to another"},
								{"question":"convey","ans":"to transfer or deliver to another"},
								{"question":"craft","ans":"skill in planning, making, or executing:DEXTERITY"},
								{"question":"creek","ans":"a natural stream of water normally smaller than and often tributary to a river"},
								{"question":"creep","ans":"to move slowly,quietly and carefully, esp so as not to attract attention"},
								{"question":"crown","ans":"to place a crown or wreath on the head of; specifically :to invest with regal dignity and power"},
								{"question":"crucial","ans":"important or essential as resolving acrisis:DECISIVE"},
								{"question":"cuisine","ans":"manner of preparing food:style of cooking; also:the food prepared"},
								{"question":"cunning","ans":"characterized by wiliness and trickery"},
								{"question":"cyclone","ans":"a storm or system of winds that rotates about a center of low atmospheric pressure, and often brings heavy rain"},
								{"question":"debris","ans":"the remains of something broken down or destroyed"},
								{"question":"default","ans":"a failure to pay financial debts"},
								{"question":"deforest","ans":"the action or process of clearing of forests; also :the state of having been cleared of"},
								{"question":"defy","ans":"to challenge to do something considered impossible:DARE"},
								{"question":"demise","ans":"DIE, DECEASE"},
								{"question":"dent","ans":"a depression or hollow made by a blow or by pressure"},
								{"question":"depart","ans":"to go away:LEAVE"},
								{"question":"depict","ans":"to represent by or as if by a picture"},
								{"question":"deplete","ans":"to lessen markedly in quantity, content, power, or value"},
								{"question":"deposit","ans":"to lay down or leave behind by a natural process"},
								{"question":"depress","ans":"to press down"},
								{"question":"dessert","ans":"a usually sweet course or dish (as of pastry or ice cream) served at the end of a meal"},
								{"question":"dew","ans":"moisture condensed upon the surfaces of cool bodies especially at night"},
								{"question":"dilute","ans":"to diminish the strength, flavor, or brilliance of by admixture"},
								{"question":"disarm","ans":"to deprive of means, reason, or disposition to be hostile"},
								{"question":"disciple","ans":"one who accepts and assists in spreading the doctrines of another"},
								{"question":"discrete","ans":"(adj.) separate; individually distinct; composed of distinct parts"},
								{"question":"disguise","ans":"to furnish with a false appearance or an assumed identity"},
								{"question":"disposal","ans":"systematic destruction; especially :destruction or transformation of garbage"},
								{"question":"disrupt","ans":"to throw into disorder"},
								{"question":"distort","ans":"to twist out of the true meaning or proportion"},
								{"question":"distract","ans":"to draw or direct (as one's attention) to a different object or in different directions at the same time"},
								{"question":"distress","ans":"great pain/cause discomfort"},
								{"question":"donor","ans":"one that gives, donates, or presents something"},
								{"question":"downpour","ans":"a pouring or streaming downward; especially:a heavy rain"},
								{"question":"drizzle","ans":"a fine misty rain"},
								{"question":"droplet","ans":"a tiny drop (as of a liquid)"},
								{"question":"ecstatic","ans":"feeling great rapture or delight"},
								{"question":"elastic","ans":"capable of being easily stretched or expanded and resuming former shape:FLEXIBLE"},
								{"question":"embed","ans":"to enclose closely in or as if in a matrix"},
								{"question":"endorse","ans":"to approve openly especially:to express support or approval of publicly and definitely"},
								{"question":"entry","ans":"a descriptive record (as in a card catalog or an index)"},
								{"question":"erect","ans":"1. characterized by firm or rigid straightness in bodily posture 2. SET UP, ESTABLISH"},
								{"question":"ethics","ans":"the discipline dealing with what is good and bad and with moral duty and obligation"},
								{"question":"evacuate","ans":"a:to remove especially from a military zone or dangerous area b:to withdraw from military occupation of c:VACATE"},
								{"question":"exempt","ans":"free or released from some liability or requirement to which others are subjectexempt:liability:pardon:penalty"},
								{"question":"exhaust","ans":"to consume entirely:USE UP"},
								{"question":"expedite","ans":"to accelerate the process or progress of:speed up"},
								{"question":"extinct","ans":"no longer existing"},
								{"question":"faint","ans":"lacking strength or vigor:performed, offered, or accomplished weakly or languidly"},
								{"question":"falter","ans":"a:to hesitate in purpose or action:WAVER b:to lose drive or effectiveness"},
								{"question":"fantasy","ans":"imaginative fiction featuring especially strange settings and grotesque characters"},
								{"question":"farce","ans":"ridiculous or empty show"},
								{"question":"fast","ans":"1. in a firm or fixed manner 2. the act to eat sparingly or abstain from some foods"},
								{"question":"fasten","ans":"to attach especially by pinning, tying, or nailing"},
								{"question":"fatigue","ans":"weariness or exhaustion from labor, exertion, or stress"},
								{"question":"feeble","ans":"markedly lacking in strength"},
								{"question":"filter","ans":"a porous article or mass (as of paper or sand) through which a gas or liquid is passed to separate out matter in suspension"},
								{"question":"flaw","ans":"a defect in physical structure or form"},
								{"question":"flexible","ans":"capable of being flexed:PLIANT"},
								{"question":"flirt","ans":"to behave amorously without serious intent"},
								{"question":"flounder","ans":"to proceed or act clumsily or ineffectually"},
								{"question":"flourish","ans":"to grow luxuriantly:THRIVE"},
								{"question":"fluent","ans":"a:ready or facile in speechb:effortlessly smooth and rapid:POLISHED"},
								{"question":"flush","ans":"to pour liquid over or through; especially:to cleanse or wash out with or as if with a rush of liquid"},
								{"question":"foil","ans":"a thin piece of material (as metal) put under an inferior or paste stone to add color or brilliance"},
								{"question":"foliage","ans":"the aggregate of leaves of one or more plants"},
								{"question":"fondness","ans":"tender affection"},
								{"question":"fracture","ans":"RUPTURE, TEAR"},
								{"question":"fragile","ans":"a:easily broken or destroyedb:constitutionally delicate:lacking in physical vigor"},
								{"question":"frenzy","ans":"a violent mental or emotional agitation"},
								{"question":"friction","ans":"the rubbing of one body against another"},
								{"question":"furnace","ans":"an enclosed structure in which heat is produced"},
								{"question":"gear","ans":"a toothed wheel"},
								{"question":"giddy","ans":"lightheartedly silly:FRIVOLOUS"},
								{"question":"ginger","ans":"a thickened pungent aromatic rhizome that is used as a spice and sometimes medicinally"},
								{"question":"glance","ans":"a quick or cursory look"},
								{"question":"glaze","ans":"to give a smooth glossy surface to"},
								{"question":"glimmer","ans":"a:to shine faintly or unsteadily b:to give off a subdued unsteady reflection"},
								{"question":"glitch","ans":"a usually minor malfunction"},
								{"question":"gloomy","ans":"low in spirits:MELANCHOLY"},
								{"question":"glorify","ans":"to make glorious by bestowing honor, praise, or admiration"},
								{"question":"glossary","ans":"a collection of textual glosses or of specialized terms with their meanings"},
								{"question":"grant","ans":"to bestow or transfer formally specifically :to give the possession or title of by a deed"},
								{"question":"grave","ans":"having a serious and dignified quality or demeanor"},
								{"question":"grin","ans":"to draw back the lips so as to show the teeth especially in amusement or laughter; broadly :SMILE"},
								{"question":"handle","ans":"to act, behave, or feel in a certain way when handled or directed"},
								{"question":"harsh","ans":"a:causing a disagreeable or painful sensory reaction:IRRITATING b:physically discomforting:PAINFUL"},
								{"question":"hasten","ans":"to move or act quickly"},
								{"question":"hasty","ans":"done or made in a hurry"},
								{"question":"hike","ans":"to rise up; especially :to work upward out of place"},
								{"question":"hint","ans":"a slight indication of the existence, approach, or nature of something:CLUE"},
								{"question":"honeybee","ans":"bee that collects and stores honey"},
								{"question":"horn","ans":"a wind instrument used in a jazz band; especially :TRUMPET"},
								{"question":"humble","ans":"ranking low in a hierarchy or scale:INSIGNIFICANT, UNPRETENTIOUS"},
								{"question":"humor","ans":"to soothe or content by indulgence"},
								{"question":"hurdle","ans":"to leap over especially while running (as in a sporting competition"},
								{"question":"ignite","ans":"to set afire; also :KINDLE"},
								{"question":"ignorant","ans":"destitute of knowledge or education also lacking knowledge or comprehension of the thing specified"},
								{"question":"imminent","ans":"ready to take place; especially :hanging threateningly over one's head"},
								{"question":"immune","ans":"not susceptible or responsive; especially :having a high degree of resistance to a disease"},
								{"question":"impede","ans":"to interfere with or slow the progress of"},
								{"question":"impend","ans":"to be about to occur"},
								{"question":"inch","ans":"to move by small degrees:progress slowly"},
								{"question":"incite","ans":"to move to action:stir up:spur on:urge on"},
								{"question":"infer","ans":"GUESS, SURMISE"},
								{"question":"infuse","ans":"INSPIRE, ANIMATE"},
								{"question":"initial","ans":"placed at the beginning:FIRST"},
								{"question":"innocent","ans":"free from guilt or sin especially through lack of knowledge of evil:BLAMELESS"},
								{"question":"integral","ans":"essential to completeness:CONSTITUENT"},
								{"question":"intimate","ans":"1. to make known especially publicly or formally:ANNOUNCE 2. a friend or confidant marked by very close association, contact, or familiarity"},
								{"question":"irony","ans":"a pretense of ignorance and of willingness to learn from another assumed in order to make the other's false conceptions conspicuous by adroit questioning"},
								{"question":"jovial","ans":"markedly good-humored especially as evidenced by jollity and conviviality"},
								{"question":"justify","ans":"to prove or show to be just, right, or reasonable"},
								{"question":"liberal","ans":"marked by generosity:OPENHANDED"},
								{"question":"linen","ans":"cloth made of flax and noted for its strength, coolness, and luster"},
								{"question":"list","ans":"a deviation from the vertical:TILT; also :the extent of such a deviation"},
								{"question":"lottery","ans":"a drawing of lots in which prizes are distributed to the winners among persons buying a chance"},
								{"question":"lounge","ans":"to act or move idly or lazily:LOAF"},
								{"question":"loyal","ans":"unswerving in allegiance:as faithful in allegiance to one's lawful sovereign or government"},
								{"question":"lyric","ans":"the words of a song"},
								{"question":"mania","ans":"excessive or unreasonable enthusiasm"},
								{"question":"mansion","ans":"a large imposing residence"},
								{"question":"mean","ans":"PENURIOUS, STINGY"},
								{"question":"media","ans":"a nutrient system for the artificial cultivation of cells or organisms and especially bacteria"},
								{"question":"mediate","ans":"to interpose between parties in order to reconcile them"},
								{"question":"melody","ans":"a sweet or agreeable succession or arrangement of sounds:TUNEFULNESS"},
								{"question":"menace","ans":"to make a show of intention to harm"},
								{"question":"messy","ans":"marked by confusion, disorder, or dirt:UNTIDY"},
								{"question":"metrical","ans":"of, relating to, or composed in meter"},
								{"question":"mill","ans":"a building provided with machinery for grinding grain into flour"},
								{"question":"mingle","ans":"to bring or mix together or with something else usually without fundamental loss of identity:INTERMIX"},
								{"question":"miracle","ans":"an extremely outstanding or unusual event, thing, or accomplishment"},
								{"question":"mishap","ans":"an unfortunate accident"},
								{"question":"moderate","ans":"to lessen the intensity or extremeness of"},
								{"question":"momentum","ans":"a property of a moving body that the body has by virtue of its mass and motion and that is equal to the product of the body's mass and velocity"},
								{"question":"mosque","ans":"a building used for public worship by Muslims"},
								{"question":"motivate","ans":"to provide with a motive:IMPEL"},
								{"question":"mournful","ans":"causing sorrow or melancholy:GLOOMY"},
								{"question":"movement","ans":"a distinct structural unit or division having its own key, rhythmic structure, and themes and forming part of an extended musical composition"},
								{"question":"muddy","ans":"lacking in clarity or brightness:CLOUDY, DULL"},
								{"question":"mumble","ans":"to utter with a low inarticulate voice"},
								{"question":"mute","ans":"to muffle, reduce, or eliminate the sound of"},
								{"question":"naive","ans":"deficient in worldly wisdom or informed judgment; especially :CREDULOUS"},
								{"question":"nomad","ans":"a member of a people who have no fixed residence but move from place to place usually seasonally and within a well-defined territory"},
								{"question":"nonsense","ans":"words or language having no meaning or conveying no intelligible ideas"},
								{"question":"novelty","ans":"something new or unusual"},
								{"question":"nudge","ans":"to touch or push gently; especially :to seek the attention of by a push of the elbow"},
								{"question":"nurture","ans":"to supply with nourishment EDUCATE"},
								{"question":"obedient","ans":"submissive to the restraint or command of authority:willing to obey"},
								{"question":"obituary","ans":"a notice of a person's death usually with a short biographical account"},
								{"question":"obsolete","ans":"of a kind or style no longer current"},
								{"question":"offend","ans":"to cause dislike, anger, or vexation"},
								{"question":"opaque","ans":"exhibiting opacity:blocking the passage of radiant energy and especially light"},
								{"question":"opera","ans":"a drama set to music and made up of vocal pieces with orchestral accompaniment and orchestral overtures and interludes; specifically :GRAND OPERA"},
								{"question":"oppose","ans":"to place over against something so as to provide resistance, counterbalance, or contrast"},
								{"question":"outgoing","ans":"openly friendly and responsive:EXTROVERTED"},
								{"question":"overdose","ans":"too great a dose (as of a therapeutic agent)"},
								{"question":"overlap","ans":"to occupy the same area in part:lap over"},
								{"question":"oversee","ans":"INSPECT, EXAMINE"},
								{"question":"pander","ans":"to act as a pander; especially:to provide gratification for others' desires"},
								{"question":"panorama","ans":"comprehensive view; unobstructed view in all directions"},
								{"question":"parallel","ans":"extending in the same direction, everywhere equidistant, and not meeting"},
								{"question":"parrot","ans":"to repeat by rote"},
								{"question":"patent","ans":"readily visible or intelligible:OBVIOUS"},
								{"question":"peep","ans":"to utter the slightest sound"},
								{"question":"pen","ans":"a female swan"},
								{"question":"pillar","ans":"a firm upright support for a superstructure:POST"},
								{"question":"plateau","ans":"a region of little or no change in a graphic representation"},
								{"question":"plight","ans":"to put or give in pledge:ENGAGE"},
								{"question":"plot","ans":"1. a secret plan for accomplishing a usually evil or unlawful end:INTRIGUE 2. the plan or main story of a literary work"},
								{"question":"pluck","ans":"1. to play by sounding the strings with the fingers or a pick 2. courageous readiness to fight or continue against odds:dogged resolution"},
								{"question":"plump","ans":"having a full rounded usually pleasing form a plump woman"},
								{"question":"polished","ans":"highly developed, finished, or refined PERFECT"},
								{"question":"pot","ans":"an enclosed framework of wire, wood, or wicker for catching fish or lobsters"},
								{"question":"potable","ans":"suitable for drinking"},
								{"question":"preach","ans":"to deliver a sermon"},
								{"question":"preempt","ans":"to replace with something considered to be of greater value or priority:take precedence over"},
								{"question":"pregnant","ans":"abounding in fancy, wit, or resourcefulness:INVENTIVE"},
								{"question":"prime","ans":"the earliest stage"},
								{"question":"probe","ans":"to make a searching exploratory investigation"},
								{"question":"prodigy","ans":"an extraordinary, marvelous, or unusual accomplishment, deed, or event"},
								{"question":"promote","ans":"to contribute to the growth or prosperity of:FURTHER"},
								{"question":"proposal","ans":"an act of putting forward or stating something for consideration"},
								{"question":"protocol","ans":"a code prescribing strict adherence to correct etiquette and precedence"},
								{"question":"provoke","ans":"to call forth (as a feeling or action):EVOKE"},
								{"question":"prudent","ans":"marked by circumspection:DISCREET"},
								{"question":"prune","ans":"a plum dried or capable of drying without fermentation"},
								{"question":"purity","ans":"the quality or state of being pure"},
								{"question":"pursue","ans":"to follow in order to overtake, capture, kill, or defeat"},
								{"question":"queue","ans":"a waiting line especially of persons or vehicles"},
								{"question":"ration","ans":"a food allowance for one day"},
								{"question":"reap","ans":"to gather by reaping:HARVEST"},
								{"question":"reckless","ans":"marked by lack of proper caution:careless of consequences"},
								{"question":"rectify","ans":"to correct by removing errors:ADJUST"},
								{"question":"refinery","ans":"a building and equipment for refining or processing (as oil or sugar)"},
								{"question":"refute","ans":"to prove wrong by argument or evidence:show to be false or erroneous"},
								{"question":"regard","ans":"a feeling of respect and affection:ESTEEM"},
								{"question":"regime","ans":"a government in power"},
								{"question":"regimen","ans":"a systematic plan (as of diet, therapy, or medication) especially when designed to improve and maintain the health of a patient"},
								{"question":"reign","ans":"royal authority:SOVEREIGNTY"},
								{"question":"release","ans":"to set free from restraint, confinement, or servitude"},
								{"question":"relevant","ans":"having significant and demonstrable bearing on the matter at hand"},
								{"question":"religion","ans":"a cause, principle, or system of beliefs held to with ardor and faith"},
								{"question":"repeal","ans":"to rescind or annul by authoritative act; especially :to revoke or abrogate by legislative enactment"},
								{"question":"repel","ans":"to drive back:REPULSE"},
								{"question":"reserved","ans":"restrained in words and actions"},
								{"question":"resign","ans":"to give up one's office or position:QUIT"},
								{"question":"restore","ans":"to put or bring back into existence or use"},
								{"question":"retrieve","ans":"recover; find and bring in"},
								{"question":"revenge","ans":"to inflict injury in return for"},
								{"question":"revere","ans":"to show devoted deferential honor to:regard as worthy of great honor"},
								{"question":"revive","ans":"to return to consciousness or life:become active or flourishing again"},
								{"question":"rider","ans":"a clause appended to a legislative bill to secure a usually distinct object"},
								{"question":"rift","ans":"BREACH, ESTRANGEMENT"},
								{"question":"rigid","ans":"inflexibly set in opinioncircular:asymmetrical::protean:rigid"},
								{"question":"riot","ans":"to indulge in revelry or wantonness"},
								{"question":"robust","ans":"having or exhibiting strength or vigorous health"},
								{"question":"rosy","ans":"characterized by or tending to promote optimism"},
								{"question":"ruffian","ans":"a brutal person:BULLY"},
								{"question":"run","ans":"an unbroken course of performances or showings,to be presented or performed for a continuous period of time"},
								{"question":"saddle","ans":"to place (an onerous responsibility) on a person or group"},
								{"question":"salient","ans":"standing out conspicuously:PROMINENT; especially :of notable significance"},
								{"question":"salmon","ans":"a large anadromous salmonid fish (Salmo salar) of the No. Atlantic noted as a game and food fish"},
								{"question":"sand","ans":"to smooth or dress by grinding or rubbing with an abrasive (as sandpaper)"},
								{"question":"satire","ans":"a literary work holding up human vices and follies to ridicule or scorn"},
								{"question":"savory","ans":"pleasing to the sense of taste especially by reason of effective seasoning"},
								{"question":"scan","ans":"to read or mark so as to show metrical structure"},
								{"question":"scanty","ans":"limited or less than sufficient in degree, quantity, or extent"},
								{"question":"scarce","ans":"deficient in quantity or number compared with the demand : not plentiful or abundant"},
								{"question":"scare","ans":"to frighten especially suddenly:ALARM"},
								{"question":"scooter","ans":"child's foot-operated vehicle consisting of a narrow footboard mounted between two wheels tandem with an upright steering handle attached to the front wheel"},
								{"question":"score","ans":"the copy of a musical composition in written or printed notation"},
								{"question":"scrap","ans":"discard;to abandon as no longer of enough worth to retain"},
								{"question":"screw","ans":"a nail-shaped or rod-shaped piece with a spiral groove and a slotted or recessed head designed to be inserted into material by rotating"},
								{"question":"script","ans":"the written text of a stage play, screenplay, or broadcast; specifically :the one used in production or performance"},
								{"question":"sculptor","ans":"an artist who makes sculptures"},
								{"question":"secrete","ans":"to form and give off (a secretion)"},
								{"question":"seemly","ans":"conventionally proper:DECOROUS"},
								{"question":"sermon","ans":"a religious discourse delivered in public usually by a clergyman as a part of a worship service"},
								{"question":"severe","ans":"rigorous in restraint, punishment, or requirement:STRINGENT, RESTRICTIVE"},
								{"question":"shaft","ans":"arrow or spear/smth long and narrow"},
								{"question":"sham","ans":"an imitation or counterfeit purporting to be genuine"},
								{"question":"shelter","ans":"to constitute or provide a shelter for:PROTECT"},
								{"question":"signal","ans":"distinguished from the ordinary"},
								{"question":"simulate","ans":"to give or assume the appearance or effect of often with the intent to deceive:IMITATE"},
								{"question":"sin","ans":"an offense against religious or moral law"},
								{"question":"sincere","ans":"free of dissimulation:HONEST"},
								{"question":"singular","ans":"distinguished by superiority:EXCEPTIONAL"},
								{"question":"skirt","ans":"to avoid especially because of difficulty or fear of controversy"},
								{"question":"skit","ans":"a brief burlesque or comic sketch included in a dramatic performance (as a revue)"},
								{"question":"slant","ans":"to present so as to conform to a particular bias or appeal to a certain audience"},
								{"question":"slate","ans":"a list of candidates for nomination or election"},
								{"question":"slight","ans":"1. to treat with disdain or indifference 2. small of its kind or in amount:SCANTY, MEAGER"},
								{"question":"slippery","ans":"causing or tending to cause something to slide or fall"},
								{"question":"smart","ans":"1. stylish or elegant in dress or appearance 2. a smarting pain; especially :a stinging local pain"},
								{"question":"smuggle","ans":"to convey or introduce surreptitiously"},
								{"question":"soak","ans":"to lie immersed in liquid (as water):become saturated by or as if by immersion"},
								{"question":"sober","ans":"marked by sedate or gravely or earnestly thoughtful character or demeanor"},
								{"question":"sound","ans":"SOLID, FIRM; also :STABLE"},
								{"question":"spent","ans":"drained of energy or effectiveness:EXHAUSTED"},
								{"question":"static","ans":"characterized by a lack of movement, animation, or progression"},
								{"question":"status","ans":"relative rank in a hierarchy of prestige; especially :high prestige"},
								{"question":"steep","ans":"to saturate with or subject thoroughly to"},
								{"question":"stiff","ans":"lacking in suppleness or responsiveness"},
								{"question":"strip","ans":"to remove clothing, covering, or surface matter from"},
								{"question":"stun","ans":"to make senseless, groggy, or dizzy by or as if by a blow:DAZE"},
								{"question":"subdue","ans":"to conquer and bring into subjection:VANQUISH"},
								{"question":"subject","ans":"one that is placed under authority or control"},
								{"question":"submerge","ans":"to put under water"},
								{"question":"suite","ans":"RETINUE; especially :the personal staff accompanying a ruler, diplomat, or dignitary on official business"},
								{"question":"surgeon","ans":"a medical specialist who practices surgery"},
								{"question":"suspend","ans":"to cause to stop temporarily"},
								{"question":"swindle","ans":"to obtain money or property by fraud or deceit"},
								{"question":"swing","ans":"something that swings freely from or on a support; especially :a seat suspended by a rope or chains for swinging to and fro on for pleasure"},
								{"question":"tackle","ans":"an assemblage of ropes and pulleys arranged to gain mechanical advantage for hoisting and pulling"},
								{"question":"tag","ans":"a cardboard, plastic, or metal marker used for identification or classification"},
								{"question":"tasty","ans":"strikingly attractive or interesting"},
								{"question":"tender","ans":"offer; extend"},
								{"question":"timid","ans":"lacking in courage or self-confidence"},
								{"question":"tonic","ans":"increasing or restoring physical or mental tone:refreshing"},
								{"question":"trait","ans":"a distinguishing quality (as of personal character): peculiarity"},
								{"question":"treaty","ans":"an agreement or arrangement made by negotiation"},
								{"question":"tribute","ans":"a payment by one ruler or nation to another in acknowledgment of submission or as the price of protection; also :the tax levied for such a payment"},
								{"question":"triumph","ans":"a victory or conquest by or as if by military force"},
								{"question":"trivial","ans":"of little worth or importance"},
								{"question":"tutor","ans":"a person charged with the instruction and guidance of another"},
								{"question":"typo","ans":"an error (as of spelling) in typed or typeset material"},
								{"question":"ugly","ans":"offensive to the sight:HIDEOUS"},
								{"question":"uphold","ans":"to support against an opponent"},
								{"question":"uproar","ans":"a state of commotion, excitement, or violent disturbance"},
								{"question":"upset","ans":"to trouble mentally or emotionally:disturb the poise of"},
								{"question":"vague","ans":"not thinking or expressing one's thoughts clearly or precisely"},
								{"question":"valid","ans":"logically correct"},
								{"question":"vaporize","ans":"to convert (as by the application of heat or by spraying) into vapor"},
								{"question":"vehement","ans":"marked by forceful energy:POWERFUL"},
								{"question":"verdict","ans":"the finding or decision of a jury on the matter submitted to it in trial"},
								{"question":"verify","ans":"to establish the truth, accuracy, or reality of"},
								{"question":"vivid","ans":"having the appearance of vigorous life or freshness:LIVELY"},
								{"question":"vomit","ans":"an act or instance of disgorging the contents of the stomach through the mouth; also :the disgorged matter"},
								{"question":"weld","ans":"to unite (metallic parts) by heating and allowing the metals to flow together or by hammering or compressing with or without previous heating"},
								{"question":"wind","ans":"air in natural motion"},
								{"question":"witch","ans":"one that is credited with usually malignant supernatural powers; especially :a woman practicing usually black witchcraft often with the aid of a devil or familiar:SORCERESS"},
								{"question":"yawn","ans":"to open the mouth wide usually as an involuntary reaction to fatigue or boredom"},
								{"question":"yield","ans":"to surrender or relinquish to the physical control of another:hand over possession of"},
								{"question":"zigzag","ans":"one of a series of short sharp turns, angles, or alterations in a course; also :something having the form or character of such a series"}     
        ],
        "medium": [
								{"question":"abolish","ans":"To do away with; annul"},
								{"question":"aboveboard","ans":"be in a straightforward manner"},
								{"question":"accelerate","ans":"to move faster:gain speed"},
								{"question":"accrete","ans":"ACCUMULATE"},
								{"question":"acquisition","ans":"the act of acquiring"},
								{"question":"addicted","ans":"be addicted to"},
								{"question":"adhesive","ans":"Tending to adhere; sticky."},
								{"question":"admission","ans":"the act or process of admitting"},
								{"question":"advocate","ans":"to plead in favor of"},
								{"question":"affection","ans":"tender attachment:FONDNESS"},
								{"question":"affiliation","ans":"joining; associating with"},
								{"question":"airtight","ans":"impermeable to air or nearly so"},
								{"question":"alleviate","ans":"RELIEVE, LESSEN"},
								{"question":"aloft","ans":"at or toward the upper rigging."},
								{"question":"amalgamate","ans":"to merge into a single body"},
								{"question":"amass","ans":"to collect for oneself:ACCUMULATE"},
								{"question":"amorphous","ans":"having no definite form:SHAPELESS"},
								{"question":"anonymous","ans":"not named or identified"},
								{"question":"apparel","ans":"to put clothes on:DRESS"},
								{"question":"appealing","ans":"having appeal:PLEASING"},
								{"question":"appetite","ans":"an inherent craving"},
								{"question":"applause","ans":"approval publicly expressed"},
								{"question":"applicant","ans":"one who applies"},
								{"question":"appoint","ans":"to name officially"},
								{"question":"apprentice","ans":"an inexperienced person:NOVICE"},
								{"question":"approval","ans":"The act of approving"},
								{"question":"approximate","ans":"nearly correct or exact"},
								{"question":"arctic","ans":"bitter cold:FRIGID"},
								{"question":"astounding","ans":"causing astonishment or amazement"},
								{"question":"audacious","ans":"intrepidly daring:ADVENTUROUS"},
								{"question":"audible","ans":"heard or capable of being heard"},
								{"question":"austere","ans":"markedly simple or unadorned"},
								{"question":"awkward","ans":"lacking dexterity or skill"},
								{"question":"backset","ans":"SETBACK"},
								{"question":"badger","ans":"to harass or annoy persistently"},
								{"question":"barbarous","ans":"mercilessly harsh or cruel"},
								{"question":"bareface","ans":"Having no covering over the face."},
								{"question":"barefaced","ans":"OPEN, UNCONCEALED"},
								{"question":"belittle","ans":"to speak slightingly of:DISPARAGE"},
								{"question":"bit","ans":"the jaws of tongs or pincers"},
								{"question":"blast","ans":"a violent gust of wind"},
								{"question":"bleach","ans":"to remove color or stains from"},
								{"question":"blemish","ans":"to spoil by a flaw"},
								{"question":"bliss","ans":"complete happiness"},
								{"question":"blunt","ans":"to make less sharp or definite"},
								{"question":"boon","ans":"BENEFIT, FAVOR"},
								{"question":"bootless","ans":"USELESS, UNPROFITABLE"},
								{"question":"brattish","ans":"an ill-mannered annoying child"},
								{"question":"breach","ans":"to make a breach in"},
								{"question":"brisk","ans":"keenly alert:LIVELY"},
								{"question":"brittle","ans":"easily broken, cracked, or snapped"},
								{"question":"budge","ans":"to give way:YIELD"},
								{"question":"buffer","ans":"to lessen the shock of:CUSHION"},
								{"question":"buffoon","ans":"a ludicrous figure:CLOWN"},
								{"question":"burial","ans":"the act or process of burying"},
								{"question":"burrow","ans":"to construct by tunneling"},
								{"question":"busybody","ans":"an officious or inquisitive person"},
								{"question":"bygone","ans":"gone by:PAST; especially:OUTMODED"},
								{"question":"cache","ans":"hiding place"},
								{"question":"cadge","ans":"BEG, SPONGE"},
								{"question":"canvass","ans":"to seek orders or votes:SOLICIT"},
								{"question":"categorical","ans":"ABSOLUTE, UNQUALIFIED"},
								{"question":"celebrity","ans":"the state of being celebrated"},
								{"question":"censorious","ans":"marked by or given to censure"},
								{"question":"check","ans":"to block the progress of"},
								{"question":"circumference","ans":"the perimeter of a circle"},
								{"question":"civility","ans":"COURTESY, POLITENESS"},
								{"question":"clement","ans":"inclined to be merciful:LENIENT"},
								{"question":"cliche","ans":"a trite phrase or expression"},
								{"question":"coerce","ans":"to bring about by force or threat"},
								{"question":"collude","ans":"CONSPIRE, PLOT"},
								{"question":"combustible","ans":"capable of combustion"},
								{"question":"commend","ans":"to mention with approbation:PRAISE"},
								{"question":"committed","ans":"OBLIGATE, BIND"},
								{"question":"commotion","ans":"an agitated disturbance:TO-DO"},
								{"question":"concession","ans":"an act of yielding"},
								{"question":"concord","ans":"a state of agreement:HARMONY"},
								{"question":"conducive","ans":"tending to promote or assist"},
								{"question":"confidant","ans":"one to whom secrets are entrusted"},
								{"question":"considerable","ans":"worth consideration:SIGNIFICANT"},
								{"question":"constellation","ans":"the configuration of stars."},
								{"question":"contagious","ans":"communicable by contact:CATCHING"},
								{"question":"contravene","ans":"to oppose in argument:CONTRADICT"},
								{"question":"contrived","ans":"ARTIFICIAL, LABORED"},
								{"question":"convoke","ans":"to call together to a meeting"},
								{"question":"convoluted","ans":"INVOLVED, INTRICATE"},
								{"question":"courtesy","ans":"a courteous act or expression"},
								{"question":"cramp","ans":"restricted; narrowed"},
								{"question":"crest","ans":"the top of a wave"},
								{"question":"crouch","ans":"to bend or bow servilely:CRINGE"},
								{"question":"cultivated","ans":"REFINED, EDUCATED"},
								{"question":"curt","ans":"sparing of words:TERSE"},
								{"question":"damp","ans":"MOISTURE,HUMIDITY, DAMPNESS"},
								{"question":"damper","ans":"a dulling or deadening influence"},
								{"question":"daredevil","ans":"a recklessly bold person"},
								{"question":"dart","ans":"to move suddenly or rapidly fall"},
								{"question":"deactivate","ans":"to make inactive or ineffective"},
								{"question":"dearth","ans":"an inadequate supply:LACK"},
								{"question":"debunk","ans":"to expose the sham or falseness of"},
								{"question":"debut","ans":"a first appearance"},
								{"question":"deject","ans":"to make gloomy"},
								{"question":"descent","ans":"an inclination downward:SLOPE"},
								{"question":"despair","ans":"to lose all hope or confidence"},
								{"question":"detour","ans":"to send by a circuitous route"},
								{"question":"digit","ans":"A human finger or toe."},
								{"question":"disarray","ans":"(n.) (state of) disorder"},
								{"question":"discharge","ans":"to dismiss from employment"},
								{"question":"disclaim","ans":"to renounce a legal claim to"},
								{"question":"discredit","ans":"to deprive of good repute:DISGRACE"},
								{"question":"disentangle","ans":"(v.) to free from confusion"},
								{"question":"disjunctive","ans":"marked by breaks or disunity"},
								{"question":"dissect","ans":"to analyze and interpret minutely"},
								{"question":"dissent","ans":"to withhold assent"},
								{"question":"dissipate","ans":"dispel; squander"},
								{"question":"doze","ans":"to fall into a light sleep"},
								{"question":"drone","ans":"to speak in a monotonous tone:"},
								{"question":"dull","ans":"lacking brilliance or luster"},
								{"question":"earsplitting","ans":"distressingly loud or shrill"},
								{"question":"elated","ans":"marked by high spirits:EXULTANT"},
								{"question":"elevate","ans":"to raise in rank or status:EXALT"},
								{"question":"elongate","ans":"to extend the length of"},
								{"question":"emanate","ans":"to come out from a source"},
								{"question":"embargo","ans":"a legal prohibition on commerce"},
								{"question":"embark","ans":"to make a start"},
								{"question":"emulate","ans":"strive to equal or excel"},
								{"question":"enclosure","ans":"something that encloses"},
								{"question":"encounter","ans":"to come upon face-to-face"},
								{"question":"enduring","ans":"LASTING, DURABLE"},
								{"question":"enlighten","ans":"to furnish knowledge to:INSTRUCT"},
								{"question":"entrap","ans":"to catch in or as if in a trap"},
								{"question":"entreaty","ans":"an act of entreating:PLEA"},
								{"question":"enumerate","ans":"to specify one after another:LIST"},
								{"question":"envision","ans":"to picture to oneself"},
								{"question":"equipoise","ans":"a state of equilibrium"},
								{"question":"erode","ans":"to diminish or destroy by degrees"},
								{"question":"errant","ans":"traveling or given to traveling"},
								{"question":"erratic","ans":"having no fixed course:WANDERING"},
								{"question":"estimable","ans":"worthy of esteem"},
								{"question":"etch","ans":"a chemical agent used in etching"},
								{"question":"evict","ans":"to force out:EXPEL"},
								{"question":"evoke","ans":"to call forth or up"},
								{"question":"exceptional","ans":"deviating from the norm"},
								{"question":"exclamation","ans":"a sharp or sudden utterance"},
								{"question":"exemplary","ans":"serving as a pattern"},
								{"question":"expedition","ans":"efficient promptness:SPEED"},
								{"question":"extinguish","ans":"to cause to cease burning:QUENCH"},
								{"question":"facilitate","ans":"to make easier:help bring about"},
								{"question":"falsehood","ans":"absence of truth or accuracy"},
								{"question":"fascinate","ans":"to be irresistibly attractive"},
								{"question":"fertilize","ans":"to make fertile"},
								{"question":"fiasco","ans":"a complete failure"},
								{"question":"flagging","ans":"LANGUID, WEAK"},
								{"question":"folly","ans":"a foolish act or idea"},
								{"question":"footloose","ans":"having no ties:free to move about"},
								{"question":"forestry","ans":"the management of growing timber"},
								{"question":"garment","ans":"an article of clothing"},
								{"question":"garner","ans":"a:GRANARY b:a grain bin"},
								{"question":"genuine","ans":"ACTUAL, TRUE"},
								{"question":"gobble","ans":"to swallow or eat greedily"},
								{"question":"goldbrick","ans":"to shirk duty or responsibility"},
								{"question":"grove","ans":"a planting of fruit or nut trees"},
								{"question":"grumble","ans":"to mutter in discontent"},
								{"question":"gullible","ans":"easily duped or cheated"},
								{"question":"gush","ans":"a sudden outpouring"},
								{"question":"gust","ans":"a sudden brief rush of wind"},
								{"question":"harass","ans":"to annoy persistently"},
								{"question":"hardheaded","ans":"STUBBORN, WILLFUL"},
								{"question":"harebrained","ans":"FOOLISH"},
								{"question":"harness","ans":"UTILIZE"},
								{"question":"haunt","ans":"to visit often:FREQUENT"},
								{"question":"haven","ans":"harbour, safety place"},
								{"question":"havoc","ans":"great confusion and disorder"},
								{"question":"hearken","ans":"to give respectful attention"},
								{"question":"heart","ans":"to give heart to:CHEER:HEARTEN"},
								{"question":"hearten","ans":"to give heart to"},
								{"question":"herald","ans":"to give notice of:ANNOUNCE"},
								{"question":"hodgepodge","ans":"a heterogeneous mixture:JUMBLE"},
								{"question":"homage","ans":"expression of high regard:RESPECT"},
								{"question":"homely","ans":"Not attractive or good-looking"},
								{"question":"hospitable","ans":"liking to give hospitality"},
								{"question":"hymn","ans":"a song of praise or joy"},
								{"question":"illegible","ans":"Undecipherable."},
								{"question":"immaculate","ans":"having no stain or blemish:PURE"},
								{"question":"indelible","ans":"UNFORGETTABLE, MEMORABLE"},
								{"question":"inestimable","ans":"Above price."},
								{"question":"influx","ans":"a coming in"},
								{"question":"infuriate","ans":"To make furious; enrage"},
								{"question":"innovation","ans":"the introduction of something new"},
								{"question":"instigate","ans":"to goad or urge forward:PROVOKE"},
								{"question":"instill","ans":"to impart gradually"},
								{"question":"insubordinate","ans":"disobedient to authority"},
								{"question":"intangible","ans":"not tangible:IMPALPABLE"},
								{"question":"interim","ans":"an intervening time:INTERVAL"},
								{"question":"invoice","ans":"a consignment of merchandise"},
								{"question":"irrelevant","ans":"not relevant:INAPPLICABLE"},
								{"question":"itinerant","ans":"wandering; traveling"},
								{"question":"jaded","ans":"fatigued by overwork:EXHAUSTED"},
								{"question":"jam","ans":"fatigued by overwork:EXHAUSTED"},
								{"question":"jubilant","ans":"EXULTANT"},
								{"question":"kindle","ans":"to stir up:AROUSE"},
								{"question":"labored","ans":"lacking ease of expression"},
								{"question":"lavish","ans":"expended or produced in abundance"},
								{"question":"levelheaded","ans":"having sound judgment:SENSIBLE"},
								{"question":"liken","ans":"compare"},
								{"question":"limber","ans":"capable of being shaped:FLEXIBLE"},
								{"question":"lissome","ans":"NIMBLE"},
								{"question":"lofty","ans":"elevated in status:SUPERIOR"},
								{"question":"lubricate","ans":"to make smooth or slippery"},
								{"question":"meager","ans":"deficient in quality or quantity"},
								{"question":"measly","ans":"contemptibly small"},
								{"question":"measured","ans":"marked by due proportion"},
								{"question":"mesh","ans":"to cause (as gears) to engage"},
								{"question":"mettle","ans":"courage; spirit"},
								{"question":"migratory","ans":"WANDERING, ROVING"},
								{"question":"minuscule","ans":"very small"},
								{"question":"misbehave","ans":"to behave badly"},
								{"question":"momentous","ans":"IMPORTANT, CONSEQUENTIAL"},
								{"question":"nauseate","ans":"to feel disgust"},
								{"question":"nebulous","ans":"INDISTINCT, VAGUE"},
								{"question":"needy","ans":"being in want:POVERTY-STRICKEN"},
								{"question":"nibble","ans":"to eat or chew in small bits"},
								{"question":"nip","ans":"to take liquor in nips:TIPPLE"},
								{"question":"nominal","ans":"TRIFLING, INSIGNIFICANT"},
								{"question":"obligatory","ans":"binding in law or conscience"},
								{"question":"oblige","ans":"to do a favor for"},
								{"question":"occurrence","ans":"something that occurs"},
								{"question":"offbeat","ans":"eccentric, unconventional"},
								{"question":"opine","ans":"to express opinions"},
								{"question":"orient","ans":"get one's bearings; adjust"},
								{"question":"overbearing","ans":"harshly and haughtily arrogant"},
								{"question":"overt","ans":"open to view:MANIFEST"},
								{"question":"palatable","ans":"agreeable to the palate or taste"},
								{"question":"pall","ans":"to lose in interest or attraction"},
								{"question":"paramount","ans":"superior to all others"},
								{"question":"partiality","ans":"inclination; bias"},
								{"question":"pedestrian","ans":"COMMONPLACE, UNIMAGINATIVE"},
								{"question":"peerless","ans":"MATCHLESS, INCOMPARABLE"},
								{"question":"perpetual","ans":"continuing forever:EVERLASTING"},
								{"question":"perspective","ans":"an optical glass (as a telescope)"},
								{"question":"pesticide","ans":"an agent used to destroy pests"},
								{"question":"petition","ans":"to make a request to:SOLICIT"},
								{"question":"phenomenal","ans":"EXTRAORDINARY, REMARKABLE"},
								{"question":"pitiless","ans":"devoid of pity:MERCILESS"},
								{"question":"platitude","ans":"a banal, trite, or stale remark"},
								{"question":"plummet","ans":"to drop sharply and abruptly"},
								{"question":"plurality","ans":"A majority."},
								{"question":"porous","ans":"capable of being penetrated"},
								{"question":"precipitate","ans":"to bring about especially abruptly"},
								{"question":"prod","ans":"to incite to action:STIR"},
								{"question":"prominent","ans":"readily noticeable:CONSPICUOUS"},
								{"question":"prophetic","ans":"foretelling events:PREDICTIVE"},
								{"question":"provincial","ans":"limited in outlook:NARROW"},
								{"question":"qualified","ans":"limited or modified in some way"},
								{"question":"rage","ans":"violent and uncontrolled anger"},
								{"question":"ragged","ans":"torn or worn to tatters"},
								{"question":"range","ans":"a series of mountains"},
								{"question":"rant","ans":"to scold vehemently"},
								{"question":"raze","ans":"to destroy to the ground:DEMOLISH"},
								{"question":"reaper","ans":"one who harvests grain"},
								{"question":"reassure","ans":"to restore to confidence"},
								{"question":"recoil","ans":"to fall back under pressure"},
								{"question":"reconcile","ans":"to make consistent or congruous"},
								{"question":"redress","ans":"to set right:REMEDY"},
								{"question":"rejoice","ans":"to feel joy or great delight"},
								{"question":"reluctant","ans":"Unwilling; disinclined:"},
								{"question":"remodel","ans":"to alter the structure of:REMAKE"},
								{"question":"reproof","ans":"criticism for a fault:REBUKE"},
								{"question":"repulse","ans":"to drive or beat back:REPEL"},
								{"question":"resonant","ans":"(adj.) resounding; re-echoing"},
								{"question":"restive","ans":"marked by impatience:FIDGETY"},
								{"question":"retaliate","ans":"to repay (as an injury) in kind"},
								{"question":"retort","ans":"to pay or hurl back:RETURN"},
								{"question":"retract","ans":"TAKE BACK, WITHDRAW"},
								{"question":"retrench","ans":"to cut out:EXCISE"},
								{"question":"retrograde","ans":"going backward; degenerating"},
								{"question":"retrospective","ans":"affecting things past:RETROACTIVE"},
								{"question":"revelry","ans":"noisy partying or merrymaking"},
								{"question":"rife","ans":"copiously supplied:ABOUNDING"},
								{"question":"roster","ans":"a roll or list of personnel"},
								{"question":"rouse","ans":"to stir up:EXCITE"},
								{"question":"rumple","ans":"FOLD, WRINKLE"},
								{"question":"ruse","ans":"a crafty stratagem; a subterfuge."},
								{"question":"saccharine","ans":"overly or sickishly sweet"},
								{"question":"sanctuary","ans":"a place of refuge and protection"},
								{"question":"savvy","ans":"practical know-how"},
								{"question":"scathing","ans":"bitterly severe"},
								{"question":"scion","ans":"DESCENDANT, CHILD"},
								{"question":"sedate","ans":"to dose with sedatives"},
								{"question":"sedentary","ans":"not migratory:SETTLED"},
								{"question":"sensitive","ans":"highly responsive or susceptible"},
								{"question":"shrink","ans":"to recoil instinctively"},
								{"question":"sip","ans":"to drink in small quantities"},
								{"question":"slew","ans":"a large number"},
								{"question":"smug","ans":"highly self-satisfied"},
								{"question":"snub","ans":"to treat with contempt or neglect"},
								{"question":"solace","ans":"alleviation of grief or anxiety"},
								{"question":"solidify","ans":"to make solid, compact, or hard"},
								{"question":"solvent","ans":"able to pay all legal debts"},
								{"question":"speck","ans":"a very small amount:BIT"},
								{"question":"spectator","ans":"one who looks on or watches"},
								{"question":"spoil","ans":"to pamper excessively:CODDLE"},
								{"question":"spontaneous","ans":"arising from a momentary impulse"},
								{"question":"squall","ans":"a short-lived commotion"},
								{"question":"stagnant","ans":"not advancing or developing"},
								{"question":"stalemate","ans":"a drawn contest:DEADLOCK"},
								{"question":"stalk","ans":"to pursue by tracking stealthily"},
								{"question":"stamina","ans":"strength; staying power"},
								{"question":"steadfast","ans":"firmly fixed in place:IMMOVABLE"},
								{"question":"stint","ans":"to be sparing or frugal"},
								{"question":"submissive","ans":"submitting to others"},
								{"question":"substantial","ans":"IMPORTANT, ESSENTIAL"},
								{"question":"substantiate","ans":"verify; support"},
								{"question":"superficial","ans":"of or relating to a surface"},
								{"question":"sweltering","ans":"oppressively hot"},
								{"question":"symphony","ans":"a symphony orchestra concert"},
								{"question":"synergic","ans":"working together:COOPERATING"},
								{"question":"taint","ans":"to contaminate morally:CORRUPT"},
								{"question":"tangy","ans":"having or suggestive of a tang"},
								{"question":"tantrum","ans":"a fit of bad temper"},
								{"question":"taxing","ans":"onerous, wearing"},
								{"question":"temperate","ans":"marked by moderation"},
								{"question":"tepid","ans":"moderately warm, lukewarm"},
								{"question":"terror","ans":"a state of intense fear"},
								{"question":"testy","ans":"easily annoyed:irritable"},
								{"question":"thrive","ans":"to grow vigorously:flourish"},
								{"question":"ticklish","ans":"touchy, oversensitive"},
								{"question":"tiff","ans":"a petty quarrel"},
								{"question":"tightfisted","ans":"reluctant to part with money"},
								{"question":"traverse","ans":"to go or travel across or over"},
								{"question":"trickle","ans":"to issue or fall in drops"},
								{"question":"undermine","ans":"to weaken or ruin by degrees"},
								{"question":"unwitting","ans":"not knowing:UNAWARE"},
								{"question":"unwonted","ans":"not accustomed by experience"},
								{"question":"varnish","ans":"to apply varnish to"},
								{"question":"veer","ans":"to change direction or course"},
								{"question":"vengeful","ans":"serving to gain vengeance"},
								{"question":"veracious","ans":"TRUTHFUL, HONEST"},
								{"question":"versatile","ans":"having many uses or applications"},
								{"question":"veteran","ans":"an old soldier of long service"},
								{"question":"vibrant","ans":"oscillating or pulsating rapidly"},
								{"question":"vindicate","ans":"to free from allegation or blame"},
								{"question":"vindictive","ans":"disposed to seek revenge:VENGEFUL"},
								{"question":"virtuous","ans":"morally excellent:RIGHTEOUS"},
								{"question":"wag","ans":"WIT, JOKER"},
								{"question":"welter","ans":"to be in turmoil"},
								{"question":"wicked","ans":"morally very bad:EVIL"},
								{"question":"wily","ans":"full of wiles:CRAFTY"},
								{"question":"windbag","ans":"an exhaustively talkative person"},
								{"question":"windy","ans":"VERBOSE, BOMBASTIC"}
        ],
        "tough": [
								{"question":"abeyance","ans":"temporary inactivity:SUSPENSION"},
								{"question":"abhor","ans":"to regard with extreme repugnance"},
								{"question":"abject","ans":"cast down in spirit"},
								{"question":"abjure","ans":"to renounce upon oath"},
								{"question":"abnegate","ans":"SURRENDER, RELINQUISH"},
								{"question":"abstruse","ans":"difficult to comprehend:RECONDITE"},
								{"question":"abysmal","ans":"immeasurably low or wretched"},
								{"question":"accolade","ans":"an expression of praise"},
								{"question":"acquit","ans":"to discharge completely"},
								{"question":"acumen","ans":"mental keenness"},
								{"question":"adumbrate","ans":"to suggest or disclose partially"},
								{"question":"advert","ans":"to turn the mind or attention"},
								{"question":"ameliorate","ans":"to make better or more tolerable"},
								{"question":"amenable","ans":"readily managed; willing to be led"},
								{"question":"amiss","ans":"in a faulty way:IMPERFECTLY"},
								{"question":"anesthetic","ans":"lacking awareness or sensitivity"},
								{"question":"annotate","ans":"comment; make explanatory notes"},
								{"question":"antiquate","ans":"To make old or out of date."},
								{"question":"apex","ans":"the highest or culminating point"},
								{"question":"aplomb","ans":"poise"},
								{"question":"apoplectic","ans":"greatly agitated"},
								{"question":"apostasy","ans":"renunciation of a religious faith"},
								{"question":"appellation","ans":"A name, title, or designation."},
								{"question":"approbation","ans":"COMMENDATION, PRAISE"},
								{"question":"apropos","ans":"being both relevant and opportune"},
								{"question":"aqueduct","ans":"a conduit for water"},
								{"question":"ardor","ans":"extreme vigor or energy:INTENSITY"},
								{"question":"arid","ans":"excessively dry"},
								{"question":"arrhythmic","ans":"lacking rhythm or regularity"},
								{"question":"artifice","ans":"false or insincere behavior"},
								{"question":"aseptic","ans":"preventing infection"},
								{"question":"askew","ans":"out of line:AWRY"},
								{"question":"aspersion","ans":"slanderous remark"},
								{"question":"augur","ans":"to foretell especially from omens"},
								{"question":"awash","ans":"covered with water:FLOODED"},
								{"question":"badinage","ans":"playful repartee:BANTER"},
								{"question":"baleful","ans":"deadly or pernicious in influence"},
								{"question":"bedeck","ans":"to clothe with finery:DECK"},
								{"question":"beleaguer","ans":"TROUBLE, HARASS"},
								{"question":"benediction","ans":"the invocation of a blessing"},
								{"question":"bequest","ans":"something bequeathed:LEGACY"},
								{"question":"beseech","ans":"to request earnestly:IMPLORE"},
								{"question":"besmirch","ans":"SULLY, SOIL"},
								{"question":"blazon","ans":"to publish widely:PROCLAIM"},
								{"question":"boisterous","ans":"noisily turbulent:ROWDY"},
								{"question":"bonhomie","ans":"good-natured easy friendliness"},
								{"question":"boor","ans":"a rude or insensitive person"},
								{"question":"brackish","ans":"REPULSIVE"},
								{"question":"brake","ans":"to retard or stop by a brake"},
								{"question":"brassy","ans":"being shamelessly bold"},
								{"question":"brazen","ans":"marked by contemptuous boldness"},
								{"question":"broach","ans":"to open for the first time"},
								{"question":"bruit","ans":"to noise abroad:REPORT"},
								{"question":"buck","ans":"to refuse assent:BALK"},
								{"question":"buoy","ans":"support;uplift"},
								{"question":"burlesque","ans":"mockery usually by caricature"},
								{"question":"calligrapher","ans":"one who writes a beautiful"},
								{"question":"capitulate","ans":"to cease resisting:ACQUIESCE"},
								{"question":"carnal","ans":"fleshly"},
								{"question":"carouse","ans":"to drink liquor deeply or freely"},
								{"question":"cartographer","ans":"one that makes maps"},
								{"question":"castigation","ans":"severe punishment"},
								{"question":"caustic","ans":"marked by incisive sarcasm"},
								{"question":"cineast","ans":"a film or movie enthusiast"},
								{"question":"clairvoyant","ans":"unusually perceptive:DISCERNING"},
								{"question":"clarion","ans":"loud and clear"},
								{"question":"cloudburst","ans":"a sudden copious rainfall"},
								{"question":"clout","ans":"PULL, INFLUENCE"},
								{"question":"cloying","ans":"excessively sweet or sentimental"},
								{"question":"coalesce","ans":"to unite into a whole:FUSE"},
								{"question":"commingle","ans":"mingle together"},
								{"question":"concerted","ans":"mutually contrived or agreed on"},
								{"question":"concomitant","ans":"that which accompanies"},
								{"question":"condign","ans":"deserved, appropriate"},
								{"question":"conscientious","ans":"Thorough and assiduous"},
								{"question":"conspicuous","ans":"obvious to the eye or mind"},
								{"question":"constringe","ans":"to cause to contract; constrict."},
								{"question":"contumacious","ans":"stubbornly disobedient:REBELLIOUS"},
								{"question":"cornucopia","ans":"an inexhaustible store:ABUNDANCE"},
								{"question":"cosset","ans":"to treat as a pet:PAMPER"},
								{"question":"cowardice","ans":"lack of courage or resolution"},
								{"question":"cozen","ans":"cheat; hoodwink; swindle"},
								{"question":"crockery","ans":"EARTHENWARE"},
								{"question":"daft","ans":"SILLY, FOOLISH"},
								{"question":"dank","ans":"unpleasantly moist or wet"},
								{"question":"dapper","ans":"neat and trim in appearance"},
								{"question":"dawdle","ans":"to move lackadaisically"},
								{"question":"debilitate","ans":"to impair the strength of:ENFEEBLE"},
								{"question":"debonair","ans":"LIGHTHEARTED, NONCHALANT"},
								{"question":"decelerate","ans":"to reduce the speed of:slow down"},
								{"question":"defile","ans":"a narrow passage or gorge"},
								{"question":"deify","ans":"To worship or revere as a god"},
								{"question":"demur","ans":"to take exception:OBJECT"},
								{"question":"denigrate","ans":"to cast aspersions on:DEFAME"},
								{"question":"depravity","ans":"a corrupt act or practice"},
								{"question":"deprecate","ans":"BELITTLE, DISPARAGE"},
								{"question":"deracinate","ans":"UPROOT"},
								{"question":"derivative","ans":"lacking originality:BANAL"},
								{"question":"desecrate","ans":"to violate the sanctity of:PROFANE"},
								{"question":"devolve","ans":"deputize; pass to others"},
								{"question":"didactic","ans":"designed or intended to teach"},
								{"question":"dingy","ans":"SHABBY, SQUALID"},
								{"question":"dire","ans":"DISMAL, OPPRESSIVE"},
								{"question":"discombobulate","ans":"to confuse or disconcert"},
								{"question":"discommode","ans":"to cause inconvenience to:TROUBLE"},
								{"question":"discompose","ans":"to destroy the composure of"},
								{"question":"disconcert","ans":"to throw into confusion"},
								{"question":"dishevel","ans":"to throw into disorder or disarray"},
								{"question":"divestiture","ans":"the act of divesting"},
								{"question":"dodder","ans":"to progress feebly and unsteadily"},
								{"question":"dogged","ans":"marked by stubborn determination"},
								{"question":"doggo","ans":"in hiding"},
								{"question":"dolt","ans":"a stupid person"},
								{"question":"dour","ans":"STERN, HARSH"},
								{"question":"draconian","ans":"CRUEL; also:SEVERE"},
								{"question":"dulcet","ans":"pleasing to the ear"},
								{"question":"dullard","ans":"a stupid or unimaginative person"},
								{"question":"dyspeptic","ans":"INDIGESTION"},
								{"question":"eaglet","ans":"a young eagle"},
								{"question":"ebb","ans":"recede; lessen"},
								{"question":"eclat","ans":"brilliant or conspicuous success"},
								{"question":"effervesce","ans":"to show liveliness or exhilaration"},
								{"question":"effulgent","ans":"radiant splendor:BRILLIANCE"},
								{"question":"elicit","ans":"to draw forth or bring out"},
								{"question":"elitism","ans":"leadership or rule by an elite"},
								{"question":"elucidate","ans":"to give a clarifying explanation"},
								{"question":"enfeeble","ans":"to make feeble:deprive of strength"},
								{"question":"ennoble","ans":"to make noble:ELEVATE"},
								{"question":"enrapture","ans":"to fill with delight"},
								{"question":"ensconce","ans":"settle comfortably"},
								{"question":"ephemeral","ans":"lasting a very short time"},
								{"question":"euphonious","ans":"pleasing to the ear"},
								{"question":"euphoria","ans":"a feeling of well-being or elation"},
								{"question":"evanescent","ans":"tending to vanish like vapor"},
								{"question":"excoriate","ans":"to censure scathingly"},
								{"question":"exhilarate","ans":"to make cheerful"},
								{"question":"exodus","ans":"a mass departure:EMIGRATION"},
								{"question":"expiation","ans":"the act of making atonement"},
								{"question":"exponent","ans":"one that expounds or interprets"},
								{"question":"extant","ans":"currently or actually existing"},
								{"question":"extol","ans":"to praise highly:GLORIFY"},
								{"question":"exude","ans":"to undergo diffusion"},
								{"question":"feckless","ans":"WEAK, INEFFECTIVE"},
								{"question":"fervid","ans":"marked by often extreme fervor"},
								{"question":"fetid","ans":"having a heavy offensive smell"},
								{"question":"figurine","ans":"a small carved or molded figure"},
								{"question":"flit","ans":"to move about rapidly and nimbly."},
								{"question":"florid","ans":"flowery; ruddy"},
								{"question":"fret","ans":"an agitation of mind:IRRITATION"},
								{"question":"friable","ans":"easily crumbled or pulverized"},
								{"question":"furtive","ans":"done by stealth:SURREPTITIOUS"},
								{"question":"gaffe","ans":"a social or diplomatic blunder"},
								{"question":"gangling","ans":"loosely and awkwardly built:LANKY"},
								{"question":"garish","ans":"clothed in vivid colors"},
								{"question":"gash","ans":"a deep long cut in flesh"},
								{"question":"glade","ans":"an open space surrounded by woods"},
								{"question":"glut","ans":"an excessive quantity:OVERSUPPLY"},
								{"question":"glutinous","ans":"having the quality of glue:GUMMY"},
								{"question":"gorge","ans":"to eat greedily or to repletion"},
								{"question":"grating","ans":"noisily,rasping,harsh"},
								{"question":"gratis","ans":"free"},
								{"question":"gripe","ans":"to complain with grumbling"},
								{"question":"grisly","ans":"inspiring horror or intense fear"},
								{"question":"grotesque","ans":"FANCIFUL, BIZARRE"},
								{"question":"grotto","ans":"A small cave or cavern"},
								{"question":"guile","ans":"deceitful cunning:DUPLICITY"},
								{"question":"halcyon","ans":"CALM, PEACEFUL"},
								{"question":"hangdog","ans":"SAD, DEJECTED"},
								{"question":"hapless","ans":"having no luck:UNFORTUNATE"},
								{"question":"harangue","ans":"to address in a ranting way"},
								{"question":"harbor","ans":"to give shelter or refuge to"},
								{"question":"hauteur","ans":"ARROGANCE, HAUGHTINESS"},
								{"question":"headlong","ans":"Impetuous; rash."},
								{"question":"heartrending","ans":"causing intense sorrow or distress"},
								{"question":"hie","ans":"to go quickly:HASTEN"},
								{"question":"hive","ans":"a place swarming with activity"},
								{"question":"hoary","ans":"extremely old:ANCIENT"},
								{"question":"hortative","ans":"giving exhortation:ADVISORY"},
								{"question":"husky","ans":"hoarse with or as if with emotion"},
								{"question":"hyperbole","ans":"extravagant exaggeration"},
								{"question":"imp","ans":"a mischievous child:URCHIN"},
								{"question":"impetuosity","ans":"Rashness."},
								{"question":"importune","ans":"beg earnestly"},
								{"question":"imprudent","ans":"not prudent:lacking discretion"},
								{"question":"impuissance","ans":"WEAKNESS, POWERLESSNESS"},
								{"question":"inanimate","ans":"not animated or lively:DULL"},
								{"question":"incinerate","ans":"to cause to burn to ashes"},
								{"question":"incogitant","ans":"THOUGHTLESS, INCONSIDERATE"},
								{"question":"inculpate","ans":"INCRIMINATE"},
								{"question":"indurate","ans":"to make hard"},
								{"question":"inept","ans":"generally incompetent:BUNGLING"},
								{"question":"ingratiating","ans":"capable of winning favor:PLEASING"},
								{"question":"iniquity","ans":"gross injustice:WICKEDNESS"},
								{"question":"insouciant","ans":"lighthearted unconcern:NONCHALANCE"},
								{"question":"insularity","ans":"narrow-mindedness/isolated"},
								{"question":"inveigle","ans":"to win over by wiles:ENTICE"},
								{"question":"irate","ans":"arising from anger"},
								{"question":"jape","ans":"to make mocking fun of"},
								{"question":"jibe","ans":"to be in accord: AGREE"},
								{"question":"juxtapose","ans":"to place side by side"},
								{"question":"ken","ans":"the range of vision"},
								{"question":"knack","ans":"a clever trick or stratagem"},
								{"question":"knave","ans":"a tricky deceitful fellow"},
								{"question":"lambaste","ans":"to attack verbally:CENSURE"},
								{"question":"lamentable","ans":"expressing grief:MOURNFUL"},
								{"question":"languor","ans":"listless indolence or inertia"},
								{"question":"lank","ans":"not well filled out:SLENDER, THIN"},
								{"question":"lash","ans":"to bind with or as if with a line"},
								{"question":"leaven","ans":"to raise (as bread) with a leaven"},
								{"question":"leer","ans":"to cast a sidelong glance"},
								{"question":"leery","ans":"Suspicious or distrustful; wary"},
								{"question":"legion","ans":"MANY, NUMEROUS"},
								{"question":"levity","ans":"excessive or unseemly frivolity"},
								{"question":"limpid","ans":"marked by transparency:PELLUCID"},
								{"question":"lode","ans":"an ore deposit"},
								{"question":"loutish","ans":"resembling or befitting a lout"},
								{"question":"lug","ans":"to carry laboriously"},
								{"question":"lull","ans":"to cause to sleep or rest:SOOTHE"},
								{"question":"maladroit","ans":"lacking adroitness:INEPT"},
								{"question":"malaise","ans":"uneasiness; distress"},
								{"question":"malodor","ans":"an offensive odor"},
								{"question":"manumit","ans":"to release from slavery"},
								{"question":"martinet","ans":"a strict disciplinarian"},
								{"question":"maudlin","ans":"weakly and effusively sentimental"},
								{"question":"mawkish","ans":"sickly or puerilely sentimental m"},
								{"question":"meander","ans":"to wind or turn in its course"},
								{"question":"mellifluous","ans":"having a smooth rich flow"},
								{"question":"miff","ans":"a trivial quarrel"},
								{"question":"minutia","ans":"a minute or minor detail"},
								{"question":"monocle","ans":"an eyeglass for one eye"},
								{"question":"motile","ans":"exhibiting or capable of movement"},
								{"question":"nadir","ans":"the lowest point"},
								{"question":"natty","ans":"trimly neat and tidy:SMART"},
								{"question":"nefarious","ans":"flagrantly wicked or impious:EVIL"},
								{"question":"neophyte","ans":"a new convert:PROSELYTE"},
								{"question":"notch","ans":"to cut or make a notch in"},
								{"question":"nuance","ans":"a subtle distinction or variation"},
								{"question":"nucleate","ans":"to form into a nucleus:CLUSTER"},
								{"question":"oafish","ans":"a stupid person:BOOB"},
								{"question":"obfuscate","ans":"to make obscure"},
								{"question":"occlude","ans":"to close up or block off:OBSTRUCT"},
								{"question":"overture","ans":"something introductory:PRELUDE"},
								{"question":"overwrought","ans":"extremely excited:AGITATED"},
								{"question":"palatial","ans":"of, relating to, or being a palace"},
								{"question":"pallor","ans":"(n.) lack of facial color"},
								{"question":"palmy","ans":"marked by prosperity"},
								{"question":"palter","ans":"to act insincerely or deceitfully"},
								{"question":"Pandemonium","ans":"Wild uproar or noise"},
								{"question":"pantechnicon","ans":"a furniture van"},
								{"question":"parch","ans":"to dry or shrivel with cold"},
								{"question":"parlance","ans":"manner or mode of speech"},
								{"question":"particularize","ans":"to state in detail"},
								{"question":"patrician","ans":"a person of high birth:ARISTOCRAT"},
								{"question":"paucity","ans":"smallness of number:FEWNESS"},
								{"question":"peccadillo","ans":"a slight offense"},
								{"question":"pedant","ans":"one who makes a show of knowledge"},
								{"question":"pellucid","ans":"easy to understand"},
								{"question":"pensive","ans":"musingly or dreamily thoughtful"},
								{"question":"perfunctorily","ans":"lacking in interest or enthusiasm"},
								{"question":"pertinacious","ans":"stubbornly unyielding or tenacious"},
								{"question":"piddling","ans":"TRIVIAL, PALTRY"},
								{"question":"plangent","ans":"having a loud reverberating sound"},
								{"question":"plaudit","ans":"An expression of applause."},
								{"question":"pliant","ans":"easily influenced:YIELDING"},
								{"question":"plumage","ans":"the feathers of a bird"},
								{"question":"ponderous","ans":"of very great weight"},
								{"question":"prate","ans":"to talk long and idly:CHATTER"},
								{"question":"presage","ans":"FORETELL, PREDICT"},
								{"question":"prissy","ans":"being prim and precise:FINICKY"},
								{"question":"profligate","ans":"wildly extravagant:PRODIGAL"},
								{"question":"propitious","ans":"favorably disposed:BENEVOLENT"},
								{"question":"provident","ans":"FRUGAL, SAVING"},
								{"question":"prudish","ans":"marked by prudery:PRIGGISH"},
								{"question":"puckish","ans":"IMPISH, WHIMSICAL"},
								{"question":"puerile","ans":"CHILDISH, SILLY"},
								{"question":"puissance","ans":"Power; might"},
								{"question":"pulchritude","ans":"physical comeliness"},
								{"question":"purlieu","ans":"a frequently visited place:HAUNT"},
								{"question":"quaff","ans":"to drink (a beverage) deeply"},
								{"question":"quandary","ans":"a state of perplexity or doubt"},
								{"question":"querulous","ans":"habitually complaining"},
								{"question":"quotidian","ans":"COMMONPLACE, ORDINARY"},
								{"question":"rabid","ans":"extremely violent:FURIOUS"},
								{"question":"rampart","ans":"a protective barrier:BULWARK"},
								{"question":"rancid","ans":"offensive in odor or flavor:RANK"},
								{"question":"rancor","ans":"bitter deep-seated ill will"},
								{"question":"rapacious","ans":"excessively grasping or covetous"},
								{"question":"rapscallion","ans":"RASCAL, NE'ER-DO-WELL"},
								{"question":"rapt","ans":"wholly absorbed: ENGROSSED"},
								{"question":"raspy","ans":"HARSH, GRATING"},
								{"question":"rectitude","ans":"moral integrity:RIGHTEOUSNESS"},
								{"question":"redolent","ans":"exuding fragrance:AROMATIC"},
								{"question":"repose","ans":"to take a rest"},
								{"question":"repressed","ans":"characterized by restraint"},
								{"question":"ribald","ans":"CRUDE, OFFENSIVE"},
								{"question":"rile","ans":"to make agitated and angry:UPSET"},
								{"question":"rivulet","ans":"a small stream"},
								{"question":"roil","ans":"to stir up:DISTURB, DISORDER"},
								{"question":"rostrum","ans":"a stage for public speaking"},
								{"question":"rubicund","ans":"having a healthy reddish color"},
								{"question":"sanguine","ans":"CONFIDENT, OPTIMISTIC"},
								{"question":"saturnine","ans":"of a gloomy or surly disposition"},
								{"question":"scurrilous","ans":"using or given to coarse language"},
								{"question":"sequela","ans":"A secondary consequence or result"},
								{"question":"sere","ans":"being dried and withered"},
								{"question":"simpleton","ans":"a person lacking in common sense"},
								{"question":"sinew","ans":"solid resilient strength:POWER"},
								{"question":"skittish","ans":"easily frightened:RESTIVE"},
								{"question":"slake","ans":"SATISFY, QUENCH"},
								{"question":"slipshod","ans":"wearing loose shoes or slippers"},
								{"question":"sluggard","ans":"an habitually lazy person"},
								{"question":"smattering","ans":"superficial piecemeal knowledge"},
								{"question":"solder","ans":"to unite or make whole by solder"},
								{"question":"spate","ans":"a large number or amount"},
								{"question":"squelch","ans":"to completely suppress:QUELL"},
								{"question":"stark","ans":"rigid in or as if in death"},
								{"question":"stentorian","ans":"extremely loud"},
								{"question":"stilted","ans":"POMPOUS, LOFTY"},
								{"question":"stodgy","ans":"BORING, DULL"},
								{"question":"striate","ans":"to mark with striations or striae"},
								{"question":"stricture","ans":"an adverse criticism:CENSURE"},
								{"question":"succor","ans":"to go to the aid of:RELIEVE"},
								{"question":"supercilious","ans":"coolly and patronizingly haughty"},
								{"question":"surfeit","ans":"an overabundant supply:EXCESS"},
								{"question":"svelte","ans":"SLENDER, LITHE"},
								{"question":"swill","ans":"to drink great drafts of:GUZZLE"},
								{"question":"sybarite","ans":"VOLUPTUARY, SENSUALIST"},
								{"question":"sycophant","ans":"a servile self-seeking flatterer"},
								{"question":"tactile","ans":"perceptible by touch:TANGIBLE"},
								{"question":"talisman","ans":"charm"},
								{"question":"teeter","ans":"to move unsteadily:wobble"},
								{"question":"tendinous","ans":"consisting of tendons:sinewy"},
								{"question":"tether","ans":"to fasten or restrain by"},
								{"question":"threadbare","ans":"exhausted of interest or freshness"},
								{"question":"timeworn","ans":"hackneyed, stale"},
								{"question":"timorous","ans":"of a timid disposition:fearful"},
								{"question":"torpid","ans":"sluggish in functioning or acting"},
								{"question":"torrid","ans":"giving off intense heat:scorching"},
								{"question":"travail","ans":"painful labor"},
								{"question":"unavailing","ans":"not availing:FUTILE, USELESS"},
								{"question":"unkempt","ans":"deficient in order or neatness"},
								{"question":"untenable","ans":"not able to be defended"},
								{"question":"valediction","ans":"an act of bidding farewell"},
								{"question":"verdant","ans":"green with growing plants"},
								{"question":"vim","ans":"robust energy and enthusiasm"},
								{"question":"vitriolic","ans":"bitterly scathing; caustic"},
								{"question":"voracious","ans":"excessively eager:INSATIABLE"},
								{"question":"votary","ans":"a devout or zealous worshiper"},
								{"question":"yoke","ans":"to join as if by a yoke"},
								{"question":"zest","ans":"keen enjoyment:RELISH, GUSTO"}        
        ]
    }
}